<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<concept id="AP-CLI-Command-Bind">
    <title>ap bind</title>
    <conbody>
        <section>
            <title>Syntax</title>
            <p><image href="/resources/images/commands/cli.png" /> <b>Syntax to bind an individual node</b></p>
            <codeblock>
                ap bind -n &lt;nodeName&gt; -s &lt;hardwareSerialNumber&gt;
            </codeblock>
            <p><image href="/resources/images/commands/cli.png" /> <b>Syntax to bind multiple nodes</b></p>
            <codeblock>
                ap bind file:&lt;fileName.csv&gt;
            </codeblock>
        </section>

        <section>
            <title>Description</title>
            <p>The <i>ap bind</i> command is used to bind a logical node in ENM to a hardware serial number. This command ensures all resources (node artifacts and MOs) in ENM are allocated to the dedicated node with that hardware serial number.
            It can be requested for an individual node or multiple nodes.
            </p>
            <p>
            When binding a batch of nodes with a CSV file, the binding is best effort. For example, when binding a batch of 100 nodes, if some of the hardware serial numbers are invalid, they fail to bind. The remaining nodes bind successfully.
            The bind command can be re-executed to over-write the bound hardware serial number of a node with a different hardware serial number.
            The command syntax and input parameters for rebind are the same as those for the <i>ap bind</i> command.
            </p>

            <p> The following options are available:
            <ul>
                <li>Bind can be requested for an individual node using the <i>ap bind</i> command with the <i>-n</i> parameter and hardware serial number using the <i>-s</i> parameter.</li>
                <li>Bind can be requested for multiple nodes using the <i>ap bind</i> command with the batch file parameter (<i>file:</i>).
                </li>
            </ul>
            </p>
            <p>The following is an example of a bulk bind CSV file with a header row.
                <codeblock>
                     [NodeValues.csv]
                     #NodeName, HardwareSerialNumber
                     Node01, SCB12345675
                     Node02, SCB12345676
                     Node03, SCB12345677
                </codeblock>

                <ul>
                     <li>
                        The CSV file must contain two columns, one column holding data
                        for node name and the other column holding the associated hardware
                        serial number.
                     </li>
                     <li>The first column must contain node name.
                     </li>
                     <li>
                        Any row in the CSV file preceded by a # symbol is ignored.
                          For example, the header row in the above illustration.
                     </li>
                     <li>The headers are optional.</li>
                </ul>
            </p>
            <p>For more information on bind see <xref href="/overview/apoperations.xml#Bind" type="concept">Operations, Bind</xref></p>
        </section>

        <section>
        <title>Examples</title>
        <sectiondiv>
                <p><image href="/resources/images/commands/cli.png" /> <b>Bind a node to a hardware serial number</b></p>
                <codeblock>
                    ap bind -n Node01 -s SCB12345678
                </codeblock>
                <p><b>Response</b></p>
                <p><pre>Successful</pre></p>
            </sectiondiv>
        </section>
    </conbody>
</concept>