<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<concept id="AP-CLI-Command-Download">
    <title>ap download</title>
    <conbody>
        <section>
            <title>Syntax</title>
            <p>
                <image href="/resources/images/commands/cli.png" />
                <b>Syntax to download sample artifacts for all node types</b>
            </p>
            <codeblock>
                ap download -x
            </codeblock>
            <p>
                <image href="/resources/images/commands/cli.png" />
                <b>Syntax to download sample artifacts for a specific node type</b>
            </p>
            <codeblock>
                ap download -x &lt;nodeType&gt; </codeblock>
            <p>
                <image href="/resources/images/commands/cli.png" />
                <b>Syntax to download all imported node artifacts</b>
            </p>
            <codeblock>
                ap download -i -n &lt;nodeName&gt;
            </codeblock>
            <p>
                <image href="/resources/images/commands/cli.png" />
                <b>Syntax to download an ordered node artifact</b>
            </p>
            <codeblock>
                ap download -o -n &lt;nodeName&gt;
            </codeblock>
        </section>

        <section>
            <title>Description</title>
            <p>
                The
                <i>ap download</i>
                command is used to download node-related samples, schemas, imported configurations, or configurations required for Auto Provisioning activities.
            </p>
            <p>
                The following options are available:
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        Download can be requested for all sample configurations (schemas and project files) for a specified node type using the
                        <i>ap download</i>
                        command with the
                        <i>-x</i>
                        parameter.
                        This parameter is used to reference sample configurations to create a project file. Optionally, no node type can be specified after the
                        <i>-x</i>
                        parameter to download sample configurations for all node types.
                        All configurations are downloaded to your local machine in zip file format.
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        Download can be requested for all initial configurations for the node using the
                        <i>ap download</i>
                        command with the
                        <i>-i</i>
                        parameter.
                        This parameter is used when you want to download the imported configurations for verification or reuse.
                        All configurations are downloaded to your local machine in zip file format.
                        Download of Baseline file is supported only when it is included in project zip file.
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        The <i>ap download</i> command with the <i>-o</i> parameter is used to download the Site Installation File (SIF) (CCF for Pico).
                         It can be executed when the node is in the following states:
                        <ul>
                            <li>Hardware Replace Suspended</li>
                            <li>Order Completed</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                </ul>
                <b>Note:</b> Configurations are automatically removed when the Auto Provisioning activity is completed and are no longer available for download.
            </p>
            <p>For more information on download see <xref href="/overview/apoperations.xml#Download" type="concept">Operations, Download</xref></p>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>Examples</title>
            <sectiondiv>
                <p>
                    <image href="/resources/images/commands/cli.png" />
                    <b>Download an ordered artifact for a node (for example site installation file for a DU Radio Node)</b>
                </p>
                <codeblock>
                    ap download -o -n Node01
                </codeblock>
                <p>
                    <b>Response</b>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <pre>Successful</pre>
                </p>
            </sectiondiv>
            <image href="/resources/images/commands/hr.png" />
            <sectiondiv>
                <p>
                    <image href="/resources/images/commands/cli.png" />
                    <b>
                        Download sample artifacts for a
                        <i>DU Radio Node</i>
                    </b>
                </p>
                <codeblock>
                    ap download -x ERBS
                </codeblock>
                <p>
                    <b>Response</b>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <pre>Successful</pre>
                </p>
            </sectiondiv>
            <image href="/resources/images/commands/hr.png" />
            <sectiondiv>
                <p>
                    <image href="/resources/images/commands/cli.png" />
                    <b>
                        Download sample artifacts for a
                        <i>Baseband Radio Node</i>
                    </b>
                </p>
                <codeblock>
                    ap download -x RadioNode
                </codeblock>
                <p>
                    <b>Response</b>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <pre>Successful</pre>
                </p>
            </sectiondiv>
        </section>
    </conbody>
</concept>