<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<concept id="AP-UserInterface-Monitor">
    <title>Auto Provisioning GUI</title>
    <conbody>
        <section>
            <p><xref href="#topology">Topology Pane</xref></p>
            <p><xref href="#status">Status Tab</xref></p>
            <p><xref href="#properties">Properties Tab</xref></p>
            <p><xref href="#project_actions">Project Actions</xref></p>
            <p><xref href="#node_actions">Node Actions</xref></p>
            <p><xref href="#validation_errors">Validation Errors</xref></p>
        </section>

        <section id="topology">
            <title>Topology Pane</title>
            <p>This pane is used to view the project(s) and node(s) created by Auto Provisioning (AP).</p>
            <p>The <b>Import</b> button is used to order an integration, migration, expansion or hardware replace for a project file, or a node.</p>
            <p>Select a valid Project File from local file system to import it.</p>
            <p>The <b>Add Node</b> button allows a user to create a single or multiple node(s) using a profile. For more details see <xref href="add_node.xml">here</xref>.</p>
            <p>The <b>Expand Node</b> button allows a user to expand a single or multiple node(s) using a profile. For more details see <xref href="expand_node.xml">here</xref>.</p>
            <p>When there is no selection in the topology pane <b>Add Node</b> or <b>Expand Node</b> allows a user create a new project and profile.</p>
            <p>Auto Provisioning supports one <b>Integration Profile</b> and one <b>Expansion Profile</b> per project.</p>
            <p>Profiles already added to a project can be viewed in the overall properties tab displayed when the top level Projects folder is selected in the Auto Provisioning topology.</p>
            <p>The <b>Search</b> box is used to locate a project or node in the Topology Pane.</p>
            <p><image href="../resources/images/gui/Topology.png" alt="Topology pane"/></p>
            <p>Expand a project to view the node(s) within the project.</p>
            <p><b>Note:</b> Enable the auto refresh by selecting "Projects" to view the latest list of project(s) and node(s).</p>
        </section>

        <section id="status">
            <title>Status Tab</title>
            <p>The <b>Status</b> tab is used to view the project or node status.</p>
            <p>Double clicking on a project or node within the table in the <b>Status</b> tab allows a user to view the project or node status.</p>
            <p><image href="../resources/images/gui/project_status.PNG" alt="Project Status Tab"/></p>
            <p>Select the Projects folder at the top of the Auto Provisioning topology tree and select the status tab the view an overview of all projects status.</p>
            <p><image href="../resources/images/gui/project__status.png" alt="Project Status Tab"/></p>
            <p><b>Note:</b> The status tab automatically updates if a change is detected on the selected project or node.</p>
        </section>

        <section id="properties">
            <title>Properties Tab</title>
            <p>The <b>Properties</b> tab is used to view the project or node properties.</p>
            <p>Double clicking on a project or node within the table in the <b>Properties</b> tab allows a user to view the project or node properties.</p>
            <p><image href="../resources/images/gui/project_properties.PNG" alt="Project Properties Tab"/></p>
            <p>Select the Projects folder at the top of the Auto Provisioning topology tree and select the Properties tab the view an overview of all projects properties.</p>
            <p><image href="../resources/images/gui/project__properties.png" alt="Project Properties Tab"/></p>
        </section>

        <section id="project_actions">
            <title>Project Actions</title>
            <p>
                When a Project is selected in the <b>Topology Pane</b>, the <b>Import</b>, <b>Add Node</b>, <b>Expand Node</b> and <b>Delete</b> actions are enabled.
            </p>
            <p>The <b>Add Node</b> or <b>Expand Node</b> button when selected in the context of an existing project allows a user to reuse an existing profile
                associated with that project or add a profile to the selected project. </p>
            <p>For more details on the <b>Add Node</b> and <b>Expand Node</b> button see the following tutorials:</p>
            <p>Add Node:
                <ul>
                    <li><xref href="/tutorials/addnode_radionode_node_centric.xml">
                        Configure and Auto Integrate Baseband Radio Node(s) with a node centric CIQ</xref></li>
                    <li><xref href="/tutorials/addnode_radionode_cell_centric.xml">
                        Configure and Auto Integrate Baseband Radio Node(s) with a cell centric CIQ</xref></li>
                    <li><xref href="/tutorials/addnode_controller6610_node_centric.xml">
                        Configure and Auto Integrate Controller 6610 Node(s) with a node centric CIQ</xref></li>
                </ul>
            </p>
            <p>Expand Node:
                <ul>
                    <li><xref href="/tutorials/expandnode_radionode.xml">
                        Configure and perform Baseband Radio Node(s) Expansion</xref></li>
                </ul>
            </p>
            <p>
                <image href="../resources/images/gui/project_actions.PNG" alt="Project Actions"/>
            </p>
            <p>
                <b>Note:</b> It is also possible to delete multiple projects.
            </p>
            <p>
                <image href="../resources/images/gui/project_actions_multi.png" alt="Project Actions"/>
            </p>
        </section>

        <section id="node_actions">
            <title>Node Actions</title>
            <p>
                When a Node is selected in the <b>Topology Pane</b>, actions are enabled depending on state and type, see table below for details.
            </p>
            <p>
                <image href="../resources/images/gui/node_actions.PNG" alt="Node Actions"/>
            </p>
            <simpletable frame="all" relcolwidth="1* 3* 1*">
                <sthead>
                    <stentry>Action</stentry>
                    <stentry>Description</stentry>
                    <stentry>Operation</stentry>
                </sthead>
                <strow>
                    <stentry><b>ZT Bind</b></stentry>
                    <stentry>Zero Touch Bind, is used to bind a hardware serial number to a node.</stentry>
                    <stentry><xref href="/overview/apoperations.xml#Bind">Bind</xref></stentry>
                </strow>
                <strow>
                    <stentry><b>LMT Download</b></stentry>
                    <stentry>Downloads Site Installation File (CCF for Pico).
                    </stentry>
                    <stentry><xref href="/overview/apoperations.xml#Download">Download</xref></stentry>
                </strow>
                <strow>
                    <stentry><b>Resume</b></stentry>
                    <stentry>
                        Resume allows a user to continue an Auto Provisioning activity if it has been suspended due to failure,
                        if it is required to wait for an on site activity to be completed or user input is required.
                    </stentry>
                    <stentry><xref href="/overview/apoperations.xml#Resume">Resume</xref></stentry>
                </strow>
                <strow>
                    <stentry><b>Skip</b></stentry>
                    <stentry>
                        Skip allows a user to bypass a failed configuration file. It allows to continue an Auto Provisioning activity if it has been suspended because of import configurations failure.
                        Executing skip can result in subsequent import configurations job(s) failure, or node integration completed without the fully expected configuration.
                    </stentry>
                    <stentry><xref href="/overview/apoperations.xml#Skip">Skip</xref></stentry>
                </strow>
                <strow>
                    <stentry><b>Cancel</b></stentry>
                    <stentry>Cancel can be used to cancel an Auto Provisioning activity.
                        Cancelling expansion can result in the node being restored to a backup if expansion configurations have been applied to the node.</stentry>
                    <stentry><xref href="/overview/apoperations.xml#Cancel">Cancel</xref></stentry>
                </strow>
                <strow>
                    <stentry><b>Order</b></stentry>
                    <stentry>Order is used to re-trigger certain workflows that have not been successful.</stentry>
                    <stentry><xref href="/overview/apoperations.xml#Order">Order</xref></stentry>
                </strow>
                <strow>
                    <stentry><b>Upload</b></stentry>
                    <stentry>
                        Upload is used to replace an existing configuration file for a node.
                        Upload can precede resume to replace an existing configuration file and then resume continues the node integration or expansion.
                    </stentry>
                    <stentry><xref href="/overview/apoperations.xml#Upload">Upload</xref></stentry>
                </strow>
                <strow>
                    <stentry><b>Delete</b></stentry>
                    <stentry>
                        Delete removes all Auto Provisioning data for a project or node from AP and ENM.
                        For Node Integration it will remove the network element if the node has never been synchronized with ENM or does not have CM Supervision enabled.
                    </stentry>
                    <stentry><xref href="/overview/apoperations.xml#Delete">Delete</xref></stentry>
                </strow>
            </simpletable>
        </section>
        <section id="validation_errors">
            <title>Validation Errors</title>
            <p>The <b>Validation Errors</b> dialog is used to display validation errors found when preparing a project.</p>
            <p>It provides the user with detailed feedback about the issues they have encountered.</p>
            <p>The export button <image href="../resources/images/common/export_button.png" alt="Export Button" /> can be used to export the table to a CSV file that is downloaded to the user's desktop.</p>
            <p><image href="../resources/images/gui/import_project_failed_dialog.PNG" alt="Validation Errors Dialog"/></p>
        </section>
    </conbody>
</concept>
