<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<concept id="AP-Overview-Expansion">
    <title>Expand a Node Overview</title>
    <conbody>
        <section>
            <p>Auto Provisioning (AP) provides an automated task based workflow that configures a node for expansion.</p>
            <p>This diagram gives a high level overview of the roles involved and some of the tasks that are automated by AP when expanding a node.</p>
            <p><image href="/resources/images/common/AP_Expansion_Overview.png" alt="Expansion Auto Provisioning Overview" height="100px" width="100px"/></p>
        </section>
        <section>
            <p>AP Node Expansion can be executed by adding a pre-created Auto Provisioning project file to ENM through ENM CLI, the Auto Provisioning GUI or by creating node configurations using the <i>Expand Node</i> in the Auto Provisioning GUI.</p>
            <p>
                The following tutorial describe how to prepare an AP project file:
                    <ul>
                        <li><xref href="/prerequisites/standard_project_file_tutorial.xml">Prepare a Standard Project File</xref></li>
                    </ul>
                The following tutorial describe how to expand a node to ENM using AP:
                <ul>
                    <li><xref href="/tutorials/expansionGUI.xml"> Perform Node Expansion using Auto Provisioning GUI</xref></li>
                    <li><xref href="/tutorials/expansionCLI.xml"> Perform Node Expansion using Auto Provisioning CLI</xref></li>
                </ul>
             </p>
             <p>
                The following tutorials describe how to configure and perform an expansion of a node using AP:
                <ul>
                    <li><xref href="/tutorials/expandnode_radionode.xml">
                        Configure and perform Baseband Radio Node(s) Expansion</xref></li>
                </ul>
            </p>
        </section>
       <section>
        <title>AP Expand Node Flow</title>
        <p>The following are some of the main tasks that are executed by an Auto Provisioning workflow when expanding a node in ENM:
            <ol>
                <li>Validation of supplied configuration files.</li>
                <li>Run node Health Check.</li>
                <li>Waits for Expansion Notification. The following notifications are received by ENM for expansion:
                <ul>
                    <li>Maintenance Button Notification *</li>
                    <li>ENM Operator executes resume</li>
                </ul>
                </li>
                <li>Sets the node Management State to Maintenance.</li>
                <li>Creates a node backup.</li>
                <li>Apply configurations.</li>
                <li>Run node Health Check.</li>
                <li>Creates a node backup and uploads it to ENM.</li>
                <li>Sets the node Management State to Normal.</li>
                <li>The node is expanded and email with node status output is sent.</li>
            </ol>
        </p>
        <p>* Pressing maintenance button will affect traffic</p>
        <p>
            1. For non-traffic affecting procedure, the ENM Operator can resume the expansion workflow directly by executing resume without entering full maintenance mode as per Step 6.
            The ENM Operator can receive the notification that new hardware insertion and deployment at site is ready from the Field Technician.
        </p>
        <p>
            2. If ENM Operator executes resume or cancel on the expansion workflow after the 1st maintenance button pressed on baseband node as per Step 6,
            the Field Technician must press maintenance button on baseband node (less than 7 seconds) again and wait for the node to quit maintenance mode (MLED light off).
        </p>
        </section>
    </conbody>
</concept>
