<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<task id="AP-BasebandRadioNode-Expansion-GUI-Tutorial">
    <title>Perform Node Expansion using Auto Provisioning GUI</title>
    <taskbody>
        <prereq>
            <p conref="../prerequisites.xml#ExpansionPreqCommon"></p>
        </prereq>
        <context>
            <p>
                <b>Objective</b>
            </p>
            <p>
                This tutorial describes the steps required to add additional hardware to node(s) and automatically apply configurations with a pre-created Auto Provisioning project using Auto Provisioning GUI.
            </p>
            <p>
                <b>Outline</b>
            </p>
            <ol>
                <li>
                    <xref href="#1">Start Expansion</xref>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <xref href="#2">Trigger Expansion (Optional)</xref>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <xref href="#3">Trigger Expansion using Resume (Optional)</xref>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <xref href="#4">Monitor Expansion</xref>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <xref href="#5">Remove Node Auto Provisioning Data</xref>
                </li>
            </ol>
        </context>

        <steps>
            <step id="1">
                <cmd>Start Expansion</cmd>
                <info>
                    <ol>
                        <li>Launch <xref href="#autoprovisioning" scope="external">Auto Provisioning (AP)</xref>.
                            <p>
                                <b>Note:</b>
                                Expansion can also be executed using Auto Provisioning CLI
                                <xref href="/tutorials/expansionCLI.xml">Learn More</xref>
                            </p>
                        </li>
                        <li>Click <b>Import</b> and select your project.</li>
                        <li>Verify the node(s) in the project are in state Expansion Suspended.</li>
                        <li>ENM Operator instructs field technician to perform expansion on site.</li>
                    </ol>
                </info>
            </step>
            <step id="2">
                <cmd>Trigger Expansion (Optional)</cmd>
                <info>
                    <p>
                        This step can be run as an alternative to Step 3 by the Field Technician
                         and is not applicable if &lt;configurations suspend="false"&gt; in the nodeInfo.xml.
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        <b>Warning:</b> Pressing the maintenance button can cause traffic loss.
                    </p>
                    <ol>
                        <li>
                            Press maintenance button on Baseband Radio Node (greater than 2 seconds and less than 7
                            seconds) and wait for the node to enter full maintenance mode (MLED light steady blue).
                        </li>
                        <li>Mark down timestamp and perform equipment expansion at site.</li>
                        <li>Mark down timestamp again once site activity is completed.</li>
                        <li>Check both timestamp's and ensures the timestamp interval is greater than 30 seconds.</li>
                        <li>
                            Press maintenance button on Baseband Radio Node (less than 7 seconds) to resume expansion workflow.
                        </li>
                        <li>Wait for the node to quit maintenance mode (MLED light off).</li>
                    </ol>
                </info>
            </step>
            <step id="3">
                <cmd>Trigger Expansion using Resume (Optional)</cmd>
                <info>
                    <p>
                        This step can be run as an alternative to Step 2 by the ENM operator once on site activity is completed
                         and is not applicable if &lt;configurations suspend="false"&gt; in the nodeInfo.xml.
                    </p>
                    <ol>
                        <li>Expand the project folder in the Auto Provisioning topology.
                        </li>
                        <li>Select each node that is being expanded.
                        </li>
                        <li>Click <b>Resume</b>.</li>
                    </ol>
                </info>
            </step>
            <step id="4">
                <cmd>Monitor Expansion</cmd>
                <info>
                   <ol>
                        <li>Expand the project folder in the Auto Provisioning topology.</li>
                        <li>Select each node that is being expanded.</li>
                        <li>Monitor the task output until the node(s) goes to state Expansion Completed.</li>
                    </ol>
                </info>
       		</step>
            <step id="5">
                <cmd>Remove Node Auto Provisioning Data</cmd>
                <info>
                    <ol>
                        <li>
                            Select the Auto Provisioning node(s) that was expanded in the Auto Provisioning topology.
                        </li>
                        <li>Click <b>Delete</b>.</li>
                        <li>Confirm deletion.</li>
                    </ol>
                    <p>
                        <b>Note:</b>
                        Removing the node Auto Provisioning data does not affect the ENM Network Element if the state is
                        Expansion Completed.
                    </p>
                </info>
            </step>
        </steps>
        <result>
            <p>The node(s) configuration is expanded.</p>
        </result>
    </taskbody>
</task>
