<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<task id="AP-PrepareBatchProject-Tutorial">
    <title>Prepare a Batch Integration Project for Auto Provisioning</title>
    <taskbody>
        <context>
            <p>
                This workflow describes how to prepare a batch project file for Auto Provisioning. A project is modeled by a zip file.
                 The file contains the configurations required by AP to execute node integration.
                 An Auto Provisioning project can contain template configurations for all AP supported node types.
                 An example of the batch project file structure for node integration is displayed below.
                 The recommended maximum number of nodes supported in a batch project is 100.
                 A batch project contains nodes which share common parameters and
                 configuration data. Batch is supported for Node Integration projects.
            </p>
            <p>It is made up of two distinct parts:</p>
            <p>
                <ul>
                    <li>A set of XML template files</li>
                    <li>A CSV file that has unique per node value data</li>
                </ul>
            </p>
            <p>
                Note: Project zip file should strictly follow the naming convention for site installation artifact file as "SiteInstallation.xml".
            </p>
            <p>An example of the batch project file structure is displayed below.</p>
            <codeblock>
                [batch-project.zip]
                > projectInfo.xml
                > nodeInfo.xml
                > SiteBasic.xml
                > SiteEquipment.xml
                > SiteInstallation.xml
                > BulkCmRN.xml
                > BulkCmTN.xml
                > substitutionValues.csv
            </codeblock>
            <p>
                The <xref href="/commands/download.xml" type="concept"> <i>ap download</i></xref>
                command can be used to download a sample batch project file.
                For more information on batch files see <xref href="/overview/apconcepts.xml#BatchConfigurationTemplate" type="concept">Concept, Batch Configuration Template</xref>
                 and <xref href="/overview/apconcepts.xml#BatchProjectCSVFormat">Concept, Batch Project CSV Format</xref>.
            </p>
            <p>
                <b>Steps</b>
                <ol>
                    <li>
                        <xref href="#1">Create a Project Information File</xref>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <xref href="#2">Create Node Info Template</xref>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <xref href="#3">Create Node Configuration Templates</xref>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <xref href="#4">Create a CSV Substitution File</xref>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <xref href="#5">Populate CSV Substitution File</xref>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <xref href="#6">Create the Project Zip File</xref>
                    </li>
                </ol>
            </p>
        </context>

        <steps>
            <step id="1">
                <cmd>Create a Project Information File</cmd>
                <info>
                    <ol>
                        <li>Create an empty project folder.</li>
                        <li>Create a <xref href="/prerequisites/projectinfo.xml">Project Information File </xref> within the empty project folder.
                            <ul>
                                <li>Must be named <b>projectInfo.xml</b>.</li>
                                <li>Must be in adherence to projectInfo schema.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </li>
                        <li>Copy the Project Information file into the project folder.</li>
                    </ol>
                </info>
            </step>

            <step id="2">
                <cmd>Create Node Info Template</cmd>
                <info>
                    <ol>
                        <li>Create a <xref href="/prerequisites/supported_nodeinfo.xml">Node Information File</xref>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Must be named <b>nodeInfo.xml</b>.</li>
                                <li>Must be in adherence to nodeInfo schema.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </li>
                        <li>Replace any site specific value with a substitution variable.
                            <ul>
                                <li>Substitution variables must be represented as "%&lt;substitution_name> %".</li>
                                <li>The substitution variables must correspond to data in the CSV substitution file.</li>
                                <li>Substitution variables are not permitted within xml comments.</li>
                                <li>Node artifact configuration template file names must match the artifact names listed in the nodeInfo.xml template.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </li>
                        <li>Copy the nodeInfo.xml into the project folder.</li>
                    </ol>
                </info>
            </step>

            <step id="3">
                <cmd>Create Node Configuration Templates</cmd>
                <info>
                    <ol>
                        <li>Create the node configuration templates.
                            <ul>
                                <li>
                                    For a listing of required configurations for supported node types.
                                     See <xref href="/prerequisites/supported_configurations.xml">Supported Configurations</xref>.
                                </li>
                                <li>All node configuration templates that are referenced in the nodeInfo.xml must have an template file created.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </li>
                        <li>Replace any site specific value with a substitution variable.
                            <ul>
                                <li>Substitution variables must be represented as "%&lt;substitution_name> %".</li>
                                <li>The substitution variables must correspond to data in the CSV substitution file.</li>
                                <li>Substitution variables are not permitted within xml comments.</li>
                                <li>Node artifact configuration template file names must match the artifact names listed in the nodeInfo.xml template.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </li>
                        <li>Copy the node artifacts configuration templates into the project folder.</li>
                    </ol>
                </info>
            </step>

            <step id="4">
                <cmd>Create a CSV Substitution File</cmd>
                <info>
                    <p>As an alternative to this step CSV substitution file can be created manually, see <xref href="/overview/apconcepts.xml#BatchProjectCSVFormat">Concept, Batch Project CSV Format</xref></p>
                    <p>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Zip all the files in the project folder.</li>
                            <li>Drag and drop the zip file into the ENM CLI.</li>
                            <li>Execute the <xref href="/commands/order.xml" type="concept"><i>ap order</i></xref>
                                command (This will automatically generate a CSV substitution file).</li>
                        </ol>
                    </p>
                </info>
            </step>

            <step id="5">
                <cmd>Populate CSV Substitution file</cmd>
                <info>
                    <p>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Populate the CSV file with node specific values.
                                <ul>
                                    <li>The CSV file must adhere to the Batch Project CSV Format, see
                                <xref href="/overview/apconcepts.xml#BatchProjectCSVFormat">Concept, Batch Project CSV Format</xref></li>
                                    <li>Each node in the batch must have a single row entry.</li>
                                </ul>
                            </li>
                            <li>Add CSV file to project folder.</li>
                        </ol>
                    </p>
                </info>
            </step>

            <step id="6">
                <cmd>Create the Project Zip File</cmd>
                <info>
                    <p>
                        <ol>
                            <li>Select all the contents of the project folder.
                            </li>
                            <li>Create new zip file.
                                <ul>
                                    <li>
                                        All files must be in the root folder of the project zip.
                                    </li>
                                </ul>
                            </li>
                        </ol>
                    </p>
                </info>
            </step>
        </steps>
        <result>
            <p>Auto Provisioning batch project zip file is created.</p>
        </result>
    </taskbody>
</task>
